

Natalia Yeromina **Graphic Designer**

(386) 302 9999 NataliyaYeromina@gmail.com 57 Raemoor DR. PalmCoast, FL



https://www.coroflot.com/ nataliya yeromina/portfolio



https://www.facebook.com/ profile.php?id=100004873841696&sk=photos

Summary:

I'm a Graphic designer with more than 12 years of professional experience in advertisement and marketing agencies. I created a variety of products of different complexity and style - from branding to billboards and business cards. I get my inspiration in new tasks, so learning of new technologies and methodologies wouldn't be a problem for me.

Desired positions: Graphic Designer.

Professional skills:

- work with the entire marketing team to develop and transform sales, marketing and product positioning concepts;
- designing and creating of company logos and brand books;
- branding of corporate and public transportation;
- creating of layouts and editing flyers, booklets, brochures, posters, internal signage, templates, banners and illustrations along with another visual materials needed to communicate a desired message to reach a target audience;
- coordinate all administrative aspects of production, including creating initial designs and receiving approval;
- checking and receiving approval for all color, copy, text, and format selections and scaling images for print production;
- preparing final designs for print or presentation;
- design for a wide variety of mediums including email, online banner ads, social media graphics and ads, lifestyle images:
- photo retouching/manipulation;
- dressing of promo actions and places of sale;
- graphic design of facades, shop windows, shops (boutiques) and etc;
- ability to work against strict deadlines and deliver on time.

Professional knowledge:

- Adobe Photoshop CC;
- Adobe Illustrator CC;
- Adobe InDesign CC;
- Corel Draw X7;
- Visual Fortran 7.1.
- Microsoft Windows
- Microsoft Office

Personal skills:

- responsible;
- creative approach to solving any task;
- fast learner;
- communicative;
- initiative and self-motivated;
- team player;
- adhere to deadlines

Experience:



Be https://www.behance.net/knd0503198a24c

Graphic designer

Mirskiy Solutions Inc, Florida, USA

2018

Responsibilities:

Graphic design for desktop applications, web-graphic design, design of icons and backgrounds

Graphic designer, technical designer

Holding "Atlanta", Odessa, Ukraine

2017-2018

Responsibilities:

- Created visual aspects of marketing materials, websites and other media, including infographics.
- Presented designs to clients.
- Checked and received approval for all color, copy, text, and format selections and scaling images for print
- Prepared final designs for print or presentation;
- Professional approach to time, costs and deadlines of creating of visual concepts.
- Developed composition and product design for advertisements, brochures, magazines and other advertising media.

2016-2017

Responsibilities:

- Worked with the entire marketing team to develop and transform sales, marketing and product positioning concepts:
- Designed and created of company logos and brand books;
- Re-pressed preparation of layouts for offset, digital and large-format printing. Advising clients on strategies to reach a particular audience.
- Developed concepts, graphics and layouts for product illustrations and company logos.
- Determined size and arrangement of illustrative material, font style and size, prepared rough drafts based on an agreed brief.

Teaching fellow of the Department of Computer-Mathematical Modeling and Web Technologies

DonNU, Faculty of Mathematics and Information Technology, Donetsk, Ukraine

2014-2016

Responsibilities:

- Taught computer graphics, information and coding theory.
- Utilized Computer-mathematical modeling in modern information technologies

Graphic designer

Corporation "Novotehnika", Ukraine

2012-2015

Responsibilities:

- Designed promotional products, visualization, color correction, layouts.
- Preliminary preparation of layouts for printing offset, digital and widescreen types.
- Worked with a marketer, teamwork in determining the style of design, format, print production and timing.
- Development of design stores and a full set of promotional products, ensuring effective sales.

Graphic designer

Advertising agency "PiArt", Donetsk, Ukraine

2008-2012

- Developed advertising models, advertising on public transportation.
- Preliminary preparation of layouts for offset, digital and wide format printing.
- Advised clients on strategies for reaching a certain audience.
- Developed concepts, graphics and layouts for product illustrations, company logos.
- Photo retouching/manipulation;
- Dressed promo actions and places of sale;

Graphic designer

Advertising agency "Aurora", Donetsk, Ukraine

2006-2008

- Prepared final designs for print or presentation;
- Developed advertising models, advertising on public transportation.
- Advised clients on strategies for reaching a certain audience.
- Photo retouching/manipulation;
- Dressed promo actions and places of sale;

Education:

Donetsk National University, Ukraine

2015

Post-graduate student, Faculty of Mathematics and Informational Technology, Mechanics of a deformable solid

Donetsk National University, Ukraine

2009

Master of Applied Mathematics, Mathematical faculty, Applied Mathematics Specialty

Hobbies and personal information:

- Lead a healthy lifestyle;
- I like to read.
- I like to learn and explore new things.